	var quizArray = [{
		"id":"0",
		"question":" What is the most appropriate software for calculating in computer?",
		"choice1":" Microsoft Excel",
		"choice2":" Microsoft Access",
		"choice3":" Microsoft Word",
		"choice4":" None of the above",
		"correct":" Microsoft Excel"
	},
	{
		"id":"1",
		"question":"	What is meant by ‘LASER’?",
		"choice1":" Light Amplification by Stimulated Emission of  Radiation ",
		"choice2":" Light Assembly by Stimulated Emission of  Radiation",
		"choice3":" Light Amplification by Simultaneous Emission of  Radiation",
		"choice4":" Light Amplification by Stimulated Emission of  Radio",
		"correct":" Light Amplification by Stimulated Emission of  Radiation"
	},
	{
		"id":"2",
		"question":"It is a personal computer operating system from Microsoft.",
		"choice1":"Microsoft ",
		"choice2":"Operating System",
		"choice3":" Windows",
		"choice4":"Computer",
		"correct":" Windows"
	},
	{
		"id":"3",
		"question":"A system in which computers  are connected to share information and resources.",
		"choice1":"ComputerTroubleshooting",
		"choice2":"Computer Networking",
		"choice3":"Computer Connecting",
		"choice4":"Computer Programming",
		"correct":"Computer Networking"
	},
	{
	"id":"4",
		"question":"What is the other name of ‘Main Memory’?",
		"choice1":"Secondary Memory",
		"choice2":"Storage",
		"choice3":"Primary Memory",
		"choice4":"None of the Above",
		"correct":"Primary Memory"
		
	},
	{
	"id":"5",
		"question":"Who is the inventor of punch card?",
		"choice1":"Jerry Yang",
		"choice2":"Jack Dorksey",
		"choice3":"Joseph Marie Jacquard",
		"choice4":"Mark Zuckerberg",
		"correct":"Joseph Marie Jacquard"
	
	},
	{
	"id":"6",
		"question":"Who is the legend of computer world?",
		"choice1":"Paul Zimmerman",
		"choice2":"Bill Gates",
		"choice3":"Ken Thompson",
		"choice4":"Jack Dorsey",
		"correct":"Bill Gates"
	},
	{
	"id":"7",
		"question":"ARPANET means ?",
		"choice1":"Advanced Research Projects Administration Network",
		"choice2":"Advanced Reform Projects Administration Network",
		"choice3":"Advanced Research Proper Administration Network",
		"choice4":"Administration Research Projects Advance Network",
		"correct":"Advanced Research Projects Administration Network"
	},
	{
	"id":"8",
		"question":"It  is an online social networking and microblogging service that enables users to send and read short 140-character text messages, called tweets.",
		"choice1":"Faceboook",
		"choice2":"Blog",
		"choice3":"Yahoo",
		"choice4":"Twitter",
		"correct":"Twitter"
	},
	{
	"id":"9",
		"question":"What kind of computer memory is both static and nonvolatile?",
		"choice1":"RAM",
		"choice2":"ROM",
		"choice3":"Storage",
		"choice4":"All of the above",
		"correct":"ROM"
	},
	{
	"id":"10",
		"question":"What is full form of BSIC?",
		"choice1":"Begin All-purpose Science Instruction Code",
		"choice2":"Beginner’s All-prior Symbolic Instruction Code",
		"choice3":"Beginner’s All-purpose Symbolic Instruction Code",
		"choice4":"Beginner’s All-project Symbolic Instruction Code",
		"correct":"Beginner’s All-purpose Symbolic Instruction Code"
	},
	{
	"id":"11",
		"question":".BAK extension refers usually to what kind of file?",
		"choice1":"Back up file",
		"choice2":"Audio file",
		"choice3":"System file",
		"choice4":"None of the Above",
		"correct":"Back up file"
		},
		{
	"id":"12",
		"question":"What does BIOS stand for?",
		"choice1":"Biological internet os",
		"choice2":"Biological Input Output System",
		"choice3":"Binary Input Ouput System",
		"choice4":"None of the Above",
		"correct":"Binary Input Output System"
		},
		{
	"id":"13",
		"question":"It is an online social networking service headquartered in Menlo Park, California. Its name comes from a colloquialism for the directory given to students at some American universities.",
		"choice1":"Facebook",
		"choice2":"Twitter",
		"choice3":"Yahoo",
		"choice4":"Google",
		"correct":"Facebook"
		},
		{
	"id":"14",
		"question":"It was an online social network founded on February 4, 2004, by Mark Zuckerberg.",
		"choice1":"Google",
		"choice2":"Yahoo",
		"choice3":"Twitter",
		"choice4":"Facebook",
		"correct":"Facebook"
		},
		{
	"id":"15",
		"question":"When was the twitter released?",
		"choice1":"March 2006 ",
		"choice2":"March 2008",
		"choice3":"March 2005",
		"choice4":"March 2004 ",
		"correct":"March 2006 "
		},
		{
	"id":"16",
		"question":"It was founded by Jerry Yang and David Filo in January 1994 and was incorporated on March 1, 1995.",
		"choice1":"Facebook",
		"choice2":"Google",
		"choice3":"Yahoo",
		"choice4":"Twitter",
		"correct":"Yahoo"
		},
		{
	"id":"17",
		"question":"It is a freeware web browser developed by Google.",
		"choice1":"WWW",
		"choice2":"Internet Explorer",
		"choice3":"Microsoft Firefox",
		"choice4":"Google Chrome",
		"correct":"Google Chrome"
		},
		{
	"id":"18",
		"question":"It is a free and open-source web browser developed for Windows, OS X, and Linux, with a mobile version for Android, by the Mozilla Foundation and its subsidiary, the Mozilla Corporation.",
		"choice1":"Mozilla Firefox	",
		"choice2":"Internet Explorer",
		"choice3":"Google Chrome ",
		"choice4":"None of the above",
		"correct":"Mozilla Firefox"
		},
		{
	"id":"19",
		"question":"When the Mozilla Firefox was officially released?",
		"choice1":"September 22, 2002",
		"choice2":"September 22, 2001",
		"choice3":"September 23, 2002",
		"choice4":"September 23, 2001",
		"correct":"September 23, 2002"
		},
		{
	"id":"20",
		"question":"It is a series of graphical web browsers developed by Microsoft and included as part of the Microsoft Windows line of operating systems, starting in 1995. ",
		"choice1":"Google Chrome",
		"choice2":"Internet Explorer ",
		"choice3":"Mozilla Firefox",
		"choice4":"All of the above",
		"correct":"Internet Explorer"
		},
		{
	"id":"21",
		"question":"When was the Internet Explorer started?",
		"choice1":"1990",
		"choice2":"1996",
		"choice3":"1994",
		"choice4":"1995",
		"correct":"1995"
		},
		{
	"id":"22",
		"question":"It is an online mobile photo-sharing, video-sharing and social networking service that enables its users to take pictures and videos, and share them on a variety of social networking platforms, such as Facebook, Twitter, Tumblr and Flickr.",
		"choice1":"Facebook",
		"choice2":"Instagram",
		"choice3":"Twitter",
		"choice4":"Photo Editor",
		"correct":"Instagram"
		},
		{
	"id":"23",
		"question":"When instagram was launched?",
		"choice1":"October 2010",
		"choice2":"October 2011",
		"choice3":"October 2012",
		"choice4":"October 2001",
		"correct":"October 2010"
		},
		{
	"id":"24",
		"question":"Who invented Instagram?",
		"choice1":"Kevin Systrom and Mike Krieger",
		"choice2":"Kevin  Krieger and Mike Systrom",
		"choice3":"Kevin Systrom and Mike Kiger",
		"choice4":"Kevin Systron and Mike Krieger",
		"correct":"Kevin Systrom and Mike Krieger"
		},
		{
	"id":"25",
		"question":"All of the following are examples of real security and privacy risks EXCEPT :",
		"choice1":"Hackers",
		"choice2":"Spam",
		"choice3":"Viruses",
		"choice4":"Identity theft",
		"correct":"Spam"
		},
		{
	"id":"26",
		"question":"_______ tags, when placed on an animal, can be used to record and track in a database all of the animal movements ?",
		"choice1":" POS",
		"choice2":"RFID",
		"choice3":"PPS",
		"choice4":"GPS",
		"correct":"RFID"
		},
		{
	"id":"27",
		"question":" __________ is a data that has been organized or  presented in a meaningful fashion",
		"choice1":" Process",
		"choice2":" Software",
		"choice3":"Storage",
		"choice4":"Information",
		"correct":"Information"
		},
		{
	"id":"28",
		"question":" The way  that computers manipulate data into information is called",
		"choice1":" Programming",
		"choice2":"Processing",
		"choice3":"Storing",
		"choice4":"Organizing",
		"correct":"Processing"
		},
		{
	"id":"29",
		"question":"Computers gather data, which means that they allow user to ________ data .",
		"choice1":"Present",
		"choice2":"Input",
		"choice3":"Output",
		"choice4":"Store",
		"correct":"Input"
		},
		{
	"id":"30",
		"question":"Computers use the  _______ language to process data",
		"choice1":"Processing",
		"choice2":"Kilobyte",
		"choice3":"Binary",
		"choice4":"Representational",
		"correct":"Binary"
		},
		{
	"id":"31",
		"question":"The term bit is short for :",
		"choice1":"Megabyte",
		"choice2":"Binary language",
		"choice3":"Binary digit",
		"choice4":"Binary number",
		"correct":"Binary digit"
		},
		{
	"id":"32",
		"question":" It is a part of a computer that you can physically touch ?",
		"choice1":"Hardware",
		"choice2":"Device",
		"choice3":"Application",
		"choice4":"All of the above",
		"correct":"Hardware"
		},
		{
	"id":"33",
		"question":"All of the following are examples of input devices EXCEPT a :",
		"choice1":"Scanner",
		"choice2":"Mouse",
		"choice3":"KeyBoard",
		"choice4":"Printer",
		"correct":"Printer"
		},
		{
	"id":"34",
		"question":"All of the following are examples of storage devices EXCEPT :",
		"choice1":"Hard disk drive",
		"choice2":"Printer",
		"choice3":"Floppy disk drive",
		"choice4":"CD drive",
		"correct":"Printer"
		},
		{
	"id":"35",
		"question":"It is  called as the heart and brain of the computer ?",
		"choice1":"CPU",
		"choice2":"Memory",
		"choice3":"Motherboard",
		"choice4":"ROM",
		"correct":"CPU"
		},
		{
	"id":"36",
		"question":"It is a set of computer programs used on a computer to help perform task ?",
		"choice1":"Instruction",
		"choice2":"Software",
		"choice3":"Memory",
		"choice4":"Processor",
		"correct":"Software"
		},
		{
	"id":"37",
		"question":"The PC and the Apple Macintosh are examples of two different  : ",
		"choice1":"Platforms",
		"choice2":"Application",
		"choice3":"Programs",
		"choice4":"Storage Device",
		"correct":"Platforms"
		},
		{
	"id":"38",
		"question":"DSL is an example of  a(n) ____________ connection ?",
		"choice1":"Network",
		"choice2":"Wireless",
		"choice3":"Slow",
		"choice4":"Broadband",
		"correct":"Broadband"
		},
		{
	"id":"39",
		"question":" _________bits equal one byte .",
		"choice1":"8",
		"choice2":"2",
		"choice3":"5",
		"choice4":"7",
		"correct":"8"
		},
		{
	"id":"40",
		"question":"The binary language consists of  ______ digits ?",
		"choice1":"8",
		"choice2":"2",
		"choice3":"4",
		"choice4":"6",
		"correct":"2"
		},
		{
	"id":"41",
		"question":"The operating system  is the most common type of  _______ software.",
		"choice1":"Communication",
		"choice2":"Application",
		"choice3":"System",
		"choice4":"Word processing software",
		"correct":"System"
		},
		{
	"id":"42",
		"question":"It controls the way in which the computer system functions and provides a means by which users can interact with the computer . ",
		"choice1":"Platform",
		"choice2":"Operating System",
		"choice3":"Application Software",
		"choice4":"Motherboard",
		"correct":"Operating System"
		},
		{
	"id":"43",
		"question":"IThe metal or plastic case that holds all the physical parts of the computer is ?",
		"choice1":"System Unit",
		"choice2":"CPU",
		"choice3":"Mainframe",
		"choice4":"Platform",
		"correct":"System Unit"
		},
		{
	"id":"44",
		"question":"The device you use to enter data into a computer system are known as _________ devices .",
		"choice1":"Input",
		"choice2":"Output",
		"choice3":"Software",
		"choice4":"None of the above",
		"correct":"Input"
		},
		{
	"id":"45",
		"question":"A computer program that converts assembly language to machine language is ?",
		"choice1":"Compiler",
		"choice2":"Interpreter",
		"choice3":"Assembler",
		"choice4":"Comparator",
		"correct":"Assembler"
		},
		{
	"id":"46",
		"question":"Which computer has been designed to be as compact as possible ?",
		"choice1":"Mini computer",
		"choice2":"Super computer",
		"choice3":"Micro computer",
		"choice4":"Mainframe",
		"correct":"Micro computer"
		},
		{
	"id":"47",
		"question":"A pirinter uses a combination of laser beam and electro photographic techniques ?",
		"choice1":"Laser printer",
		"choice2":"DOT matrix",
		"choice3":"Line printer",
		"choice4":"All of the above",
		"correct":"Laser printer"
		},
		{
	"id":"48",
		"question":"When was Apple Macintosh II microcomputer introduced in the market ?",
		"choice1":"1964",
		"choice2":"1970",
		"choice3":"1983",
		"choice4":"1986",
		"correct":"1983"
		},
		{
	"id":"49",
		"question":"Human beings are referred to as Homosapiens, which device is called Silico Sapiens ?",
		"choice1":"Monitor",
		"choice2":"Hardware",
		"choice3":"Robot",
		"choice4":"Computer",
		"correct":"Computer"
		},
		{
	"id":"50",
		"question":"When was punched card equipment used for the first time to process the British sensor ?",
		"choice1":"1910",
		"choice2":"1909",
		"choice3":"1911",
		"choice4":"1908",
		"correct":"1911"
		},
		{
	"id":"51",
		"question":"Which of the following is not an example of Operating System?",
		"choice1":"Windows 98",
		"choice2":"MS Office Xp",
		"choice3":"BSD Unix",
		"choice4":"Red Hat Linux",
		"correct":"MS Office Xp"
		},
		{
	"id":"52",
		"question":"The errors that can be pointed by the compiler are ?",
		"choice1":"Syntax error",
		"choice2":"Symantiic error",
		"choice3":"Logical error",
		"choice4":"Internal error",
		"correct":"Syntax error"
		},
		{
	"id":"53",
		"question":"What do you use to create a chart ?",
		"choice1":"Pie Wizard",
		"choice2":"Excel Wizard",
		"choice3":"Data Wizard",
		"choice4":"Chart Wizard",
		"correct":"Chart Wizard"
		},
		{
	"id":"54",
		"question":"IC chips used in computers are usually made of  _______.",
		"choice1":"Lead",
		"choice2":"Silicon",
		"choice3":"Chromium",
		"choice4":"Gold",
		"correct":"Silicon"
		},
		{
	"id":"55",
		"question":"One kilobyte is equal to ?",
		"choice1":"1000 bytes",
		"choice2":"100 bytes",
		"choice3":"1024 bytes",
		"choice4":"1023 bytes",
		"correct":"1024 bytes"
		},
		{
	"id":"56",
		"question":"The most widely used computer device is ?",
		"choice1":"Solid State Disk",
		"choice2":"Internal Hard Disk",
		"choice3":"External Hard disk",
		"choice4":"All of the above",
		"correct":"Internal Hard Disk"
		},
		{
	"id":"57",
		"question":"Who is the father of Modern computer .",
		"choice1":"Abraham Lincoln",
		"choice2":"James Gosling",
		"choice3":"Charles Babbage",
		"choice4":"Gordon E. Moore",
		"correct":"Charles Babbage"
		},
		{
	"id":"58",
		"question":"The first generation computers used for circuitry ?",
		"choice1":"Vacuum tube",
		"choice2":"Transistors",
		"choice3":"Integrated Circuits",
		"choice4":"None of the above",
		"correct":"Vacuum tube"
		},
		{
	"id":"59",
		"question":"The main working memory used by the computer are :",
		"choice1":"RAM",
		"choice2":"ROM",
		"choice3":"DVD",
		"choice4":"CD",
		"correct":"RAM"
		},
		{
	"id":"60",
		"question":"ROM is a type of memory ?",
		"choice1":"Volatile",
		"choice2":"Non volatile",
		"choice3":"Dynamic",
		"choice4":"All of the above",
		"correct":"Non volatile"
		},
		{
	"id":"61",
		"question":"_______ are harmful to computer operation ?",
		"choice1":"C Language",
		"choice2":"Virus",
		"choice3":"Fortran",
		"choice4":"None of the above",
		"correct":"Virus"
		},
		{
	"id":"62",
		"question":"The first phone to run on the Android OS was the HTC Dream which was launched on ? ",
		"choice1":"22 October 2008",
		"choice2":"22 October 2010",
		"choice3":"22 October 2004",
		"choice4":"22 October 2006",
		"correct":"22 October 2008"
		},
		{
	"id":"63",
		"question":"  Android 1.5 is also known as ____________.",
		"choice1":"Android Cream",
		"choice2":"Android Eclair",
		"choice3":"Android Donut",
		"choice4":"Android Cupcake",
		"correct":"Android Cupcake"
		},
		{
	"id":"64",
		"question":" Android 2.2 is also known as ____________.",
		"choice1":"Android FroYo",
		"choice2":"Android Cupcake",
		"choice3":"Android Donut",
		"choice4":"None of the above",
		"correct":"Android FroYo"
		},
		{
	"id":"65",
		"question":"______________is a system of interlinked hypertext documents that are accessed via the Internet ?",
		"choice1":"Web Browser",
		"choice2":"Website",
		"choice3":"World Wide Web ",
		"choice4":"None of the above",
		"correct":"World Wide Web "
		},
		{
	"id":"66",
		"question":" It is a numerical label assigned to each device participating in a computer network that uses the Internet Protocol for communication ?",
		"choice1":"IP Address",
		"choice2":"Web Address",
		"choice3":"Protocol",
		"choice4":"None of the above",
		"correct":"IP Address"
		},
		{
	"id":"67",
		"question":"_____________is a video-sharing website headquartered in San Bruno, California. The site allows users to upload, view, and share videos.",
		"choice1":"Web Browser",
		"choice2":"Youtube",
		"choice3":"Google",
		"choice4":"Video Viewer",
		"correct":"Youtube"
		},
		{
	"id":"68",
		"question":" It is a device that detects events or changes in quantities and provides a corresponding output, generally as an electrical or optical signal;",
		"choice1":"Sensor",
		"choice2":"Detector",
		"choice3":"Flash",
		"choice4":"None of the above",
		"correct":"Sensor"
		},
		{
	"id":"69",
		"question":"A__________ is an optical machine-readable representation of data relating to the object to which it is attached. ",
		"choice1":"Code",
		"choice2":"Sensor	",
		"choice3":" Barcode",
		"choice4":"Touch Code",
		"correct":" Barcode"
		},
		{
	"id":"70",
		"question":"It is a portable personal computer with a clamshell form factor, suitable for mobile use. They are also sometimes called notebook computers or notebooks. ",
		"choice1":"Computer",
		"choice2":"Tablet",
		"choice3":"Laptop",
		"choice4":"All of the above",
		"correct":"Laptop"
		},
		{
	"id":"71",
		"question":"__________a hand-operated electronic device that controls the coordinates of a cursor on your computer screen as you move it around on a padcomputer ?",
		"choice1":"Computer Mouse",
		"choice2":"Computer Pointer",
		"choice3":"Connector	",
		"choice4":"None of the above",
		"correct":"Computer Mouse"
		},
		{
	"id":"72",
		"question":"It is a typewriter-style device, which uses an arrangement of buttons or keys, to act as mechanical levers or electronic switches",
		"choice1":"Computer Mouse",
		"choice2":"Computer Keyboard",
		"choice3":"Desktop",
		"choice4":"None of the above",
		"correct":"Computer Keyboard"
		},
		{
	"id":"73",
		"question":"It is a global system of interconnected computer networks that use the standard Internet protocol suite (TCP/IP) to link several billion devices worldwide. ",
		"choice1":"Intranet",
		"choice2":"Address",
		"choice3":"Internet",
		"choice4":"Connection",
		"correct":"Internet"
		},
		{
	"id":"74",
		"question":"______________a farming simulation social network game developed by Zynga in 2009. It is similar to Happy Farm, Farm Town, and video games such as the Harvest Moon series.[",
		"choice1":"Farm ville",
		"choice2":"Candy Crush	",
		"choice3":"Happy ville",
		"choice4":"None of the above",
		"correct":"Farm ville"
		},
		{
	"id":"75",
		"question":"____________a word processor and was previously considered the main program in Office. It was first announced by Bill Gates of Microsoft on August 1, 1988 at COMDEX in Las Vegas. ",
		"choice1":"MS Excel",
		"choice2":"MS PowerPoint",
		"choice3":"MS Access",
		"choice4":"MS Word",
		"correct":"MS Word"
		},
		{
	"id":"76",
		"question":"It is a spreadsheet program that originally competed with the dominant Lotus 1-2-3, and eventually outsold it",
		"choice1":"MS Excel",
		"choice2":"MS Word",
		"choice3":"MS PowerPoint",
		"choice4":"MS Access",
		"correct":"MS Excel"
		},
		{
	"id":"77",
		"question":"______________is a database management system for Windows, that combines the relational Microsoft Jet Database Engine with a graphical user interface and software-development tools. ",
		"choice1":"MS Word",
		"choice2":"MS Powerpoint",
		"choice3":"MS Access",
		"choice4":"MS Excel",
		"correct":"MS Access"
		},
		{
	"id":"78",
		"question":" It is used to create slideshows, composed of text, graphics, and other objects, which can be displayed on-screen and shown by the presenter or printed out on transparencies or slides.",
		"choice1":"MS Access",
		"choice2":"MS Powerpoint",
		"choice3":"MS Excel",
		"choice4":"MS Word",
		"correct":"MS Powerpoint"
		},
		{
	"id":"79",
		"question":"It is a file format used to present documents in a manner independent of application software, hardware, and operating systems.[",
		"choice1":"PDF",
		"choice2":"MS Word",
		"choice3":"Notepad	",
		"choice4":"All of the above",
		"correct":"PDF"
		},
		{
	"id":"80",
		"question":"________is a simple graphics painting program that has been included with all versions of Microsoft Windows.",
		"choice1":"Photo Editor	",
		"choice2":"Paint",
		"choice3":"Photoshop",
		"choice4":"MS Drawing",
		"correct":"Paint"
		},
		{
	"id":"81",
		"question":"It is a generic text editor included with Microsoft Windows that enables someone to open and read plaintext files.",
		"choice1":"Notebook",
		"choice2":"MS Word",
		"choice3":"Notepad",
		"choice4":"None of the above",
		"correct":"Notepad"
		},
		{
	"id":"82",
		"question":"It is a data storage device that includes flash memory and it is typically removable and rewritable,  ",
		"choice1":"Flash Drive",
		"choice2":"Flash File",
		"choice3":"Flash Bus",
		"choice4":"None of the above",
		"correct":"Flash Drive"
		},
		{
	"id":"83",
		"question":"_________ is a portable usually cordless telephone for use in a cellular system .  ",
		"choice1":"Phone Call",
		"choice2":"Telephone	",
		"choice3":"Cellphone",
		"choice4":"All of the above",
		"correct":"Cellphone"
		},
		{
	"id":"84",
		"question":"It is a GSM cellular phone, announced by Nokia on March 18, 1999.[1] With 160 million units sold,[2][3] the 3210 is one of the most popular and successful phones in history.",
		"choice1":"Nokia3210	",
		"choice2":"Nokia3120",
		"choice3":"Nokia 2310",
		"choice4":"None of the above",
		"correct":"Nokia3210"
		},
		{
	"id":"85",
		"question":" It is a telecommunications device that permits two or more users to conduct a conversation when they are not in the same vicinity of each other to be heard directly. ",
		"choice1":"Microphone",
		"choice2":"Telephone	",
		"choice3":"Cellphone",
		"choice4":"All of the above",
		"correct":"Telephone"
		},
		{
	"id":"86",
		"question":"_________ is an electronic visual display for computers.It comprises the display device, circuitry and an enclosure. ",
		"choice1":"LCD",
		"choice2":"Projector",
		"choice3":"Monitor",
		"choice4":"None of the above",
		"correct":"Monitor"
		},
		{
	"id":"87",
		"question":"It is a raster graphics editor developed and published by Adobe Systems for Windows and OS X.",
		"choice1":"Adobe Photoshop",
		"choice2":"Photoscape",
		"choice3":"PhotoBoot",
		"choice4":"None of the above",
		"correct":"Adobe Photoshop"
		},
		{
	"id":"88",
		"question":"It is the standard markup language used to create web pages.",
		"choice1":"HMTL",
		"choice2":"HLMT",
		"choice3":"HTML",
		"choice4":"HMLT",
		"correct":"HTML"
		},
		{
	"id":"89",
		"question":"It can be used to create programs to control the behavior of a machine or to express algorithms. ",
		"choice1":"Programming	",
		"choice2":"Programmer",
		"choice3":"Program",
		"choice4":"None of the above",
		"correct":"Programming"
		},
		{
	"id":"90",
		"question":"It is a computer programming language that is concurrent, class-based, object-oriented, and specifically designed to have as few implementation dependencies as possible. ",
		"choice1":"Netscape",
		"choice2":"Java",
		"choice3":"JCreator",
		"choice4":"All of the above",
		"correct":"Java"
		},
		{
	"id":"91",
		"question":"It is a digital distribution platform operated by Google. It  allow users to browse and download applications developed with the Android SDK and published through Google",
		"choice1":"Google Play",
		"choice2":"Blackberry AppWorld",
		"choice3":"Apple App",
		"choice4":"None of the above",
		"correct":"Google Play"
		},
		{
	"id":"92",
		"question":"The ______________Store is an online store for purchasing and downloading software applications and mobile apps for Apple computers and devices.",
		"choice1":"Blackberry App",
		"choice2":"Apple App Store",
		"choice3":"Google Play",
		"choice4":"None of the above",
		"correct":"Apple App Store"
		},
		{
	"id":"93",
		"question":"It is a calculating tool that was in use centuries before the adoption of the written modern numeral system and is still widely used by merchants, traders and clerks in Asia, Africa, and elsewhere. ",
		"choice1":"Abacus",
		"choice2":"Calculator",
		"choice3":"Laptop",
		"choice4":"All of the above",
		"correct":"Abacus"
		},
		{
	"id":"94",
		"question":"It is a video camera that feeds or streams its image in real time to or through a computer to computer network.",
		"choice1":"Cellphone",
		"choice2":"Camera",
		"choice3":"Webcam",
		"choice4":"None of the above",
		"correct":"Webcam"
		},
		{
	"id":"95",
		"question":" It is a computer game included with Microsoft Windows, based on a card game of the same name. ",
		"choice1":"Solitaire",
		"choice2":"Candy Crush",
		"choice3":"Cards",
		"choice4":"None of the above",
		"correct":"Solitaire"
		},
		{
	"id":"96",
		"question":"It is the official app store for BlackBerry smartphones and tablets.",
		"choice1":"Google Play",
		"choice2":"Blackberry App World",
		"choice3":"Apple App",
		"choice4":"None of the above",
		"correct":"Blackberry App World"
		},
		{
	"id":"97",
		"question":"___________ are super-thin displays that are used in laptop computer screens and flat panel monitors. ",
		"choice1":"Projector",
		"choice2":"LCD",
		"choice3":"Monitor",
		"choice4":"None of the above",
		"correct":"LCD"
		},
		{
	"id":"98",
		"question":"Android 2.0/2.1 is also known as ____________.",
		"choice1":"Android Eclair",
		"choice2":"Android Cupcake",
		"choice3":"Android Food",
		"choice4":"All of the above",
		"correct":"Android Eclair"
		},
		{
	"id":"99",
		"question":"It is hosted on at least one web server, accessible via a network such as the Internet or a private local area network through an Internet address known as a Uniform resource locator. ",
		"choice1":"Internet",
		"choice2":"WWW",
		"choice3":"Website",
		"choice4":"None of the above",
		"correct":"Website"
		},
		
		
	]
	
	